[Music]
[Música]
It's true that it was the Dallas thing about
es verdad queé fue lo de Dallas de
Germán, man, I was going to watch it yesterday,
Germán tío lo iba a ver ayer es que en
actually today I was going to record the news, man,
realidad hoy iba a grabar noticiero tío
but I didn't have time because it was
pero no me ha dado lugar porque se me ha
super late so I don't know if he's around
hecho super tarde entonces no sé si está
here places but if you're around here, the news that we do
por aquí lugares pero si estás por aquí
n't cover, leave it,
las noticias que no tratemos dejalas
okay, the news that we don't cover, leave
vale las noticias que no tratemos
it for the news, okay And tomorrow
dejalas para el noti vale Y mañana
fill it out, okay, fill it out And tomorrow at
rellénalo vale rellénalo Y mañana al
noon like this I'll record the news about the salsería
mediodía así grabo noti de la salsería
because we have abandoned the news about the
que tenemos abandonados los noti de la
salsería and we'll see what's up with
salsería y vamos a ver queé es lo de
Dallas Dallas announces powerful video
Dallas Dallas anuncia vídeo potente
about youtuber Oh but he didn't say
sobre youtuber Ah pero no ha dicho A
who Oh he didn't say a name and why
quién Ah que no dijo nombre y por qué
is everyone on Twitter saying it
está todo el mundo en Twitter diciendo
's Germán, I mean, I've seen a lot
que es a Germán o sea he visto un montón
of people on Twitter like that, forget about Germán,
de gente en Twitter del palo olvida
you don't even run into him anymore please
Germán ya él ni te topa por favor
forget about him I'm telling you it's coming strong
olvídalo ya os digo que se viene fuerte
and prepared for a few days of really strong hate,
y preparado por unos días de mucho hate
prepared I'm just telling you
fuertísimo preparados solo os digo
prepared it's going to be strong I
preparados va a estar fuerte Yo de
really think this thing about people, the
verdad el tema este de de la gente el
support and saying, Oh, I'll follow you, I'll let you say it
apoyo y decir Ay te sigo te dejo decir
's  for me the story always seems like a
es para mí la historia siempre me parece
lot of having already reached the
mucho ya haber llegado a los
subscribers arrived within YouTube
suscriptores llegado dentro de YouTube
Because well at the end of the day on YouTube
Porque bueno a fin de cuentas en YouTube
nobody sees who you follow Unless you
nadie ve a quién sigues A menos que
have an audience no but it's something like
tengas público no pero es algo como que
the subscriptions are closed
las suscripciones están cerradas
so this is where they follow me the most
entonces aquí es donde más me sigue Tal
Maybe because I feel that their friends aren't going to
vez porque siento que así sus amigos no
judge them I think but on other
les van a juzgar pienso per en otras
social networks they don't follow me as much Because
redes sociales no me siguen tanto Porque
the follows are public if you
las las los follows son públicos si me
follow me on Twitter anyone can see
sigues en Twitter cualquier persona ve
that you follow me on Twitter if you follow me on
que me sigues en Twitter si me sigues en
Instagram anyone can see that you
instagram cualquier persona ve que me
follow me on Instagram so I understand the
sigues en instagram entonces entiendo el
point but of course I don't know if you're
punto pero claro No sé si se está
referring to streamer not influencer no I
refiriendo a streamer no influencer no
think there may be many
yo creo que puede que haya muchos
influencers Maybe not that they
influencers A lo mejor que no que te
follow you on YouTube but don't follow you on
siguen en YouTube pero no te siguen en
Instagram there are many of me there are
instagram a mí hay muchos a mí hay
many influencers that maybe
muchos influencers que a lo mejor de
suddenly talk to me and I say see me no eh and it
repente me hablan y digoo me ve no eh y
turns out that I don't follow you I watch the videos
resulta que no te sigo veo los vídeos
that I watch the little room and damn they don't follow me not
que veo el salito y [__] no me sigu ni
on Instagram or on Twitter or
en instagram ni en Twitter ni en ninguna
anywhere the least I imagined it was a
parte que menos me imaginaba era un
message from this person and normally what I
mensaje de esta persona y normalmente lo
do is not even answer because I  I don't
que hago es ni contestar porque yo no
want to talk to anyone no but but it's
quiero hablar con nadie no pero pero es
like Yes of course so that publicly
como Sí claro para que públicamente la
people don't know What type of content you see
gente no sepa Qué tipo de contenido ves
not like here on YouTube they follow me more I
no como que aquí YouTube me sigen más yo
think That's why they're not going to
pienso Por eso porque no les van a
judge them seeing that someone is subscribed
juzgar viendo que alguien está suscrito
to me and I have this thing about
a mí y yo el tema este de de los
subscribers the people who get angry and
suscriptores la gente que se enfada y
apply the subscription punishment Sao
aplica la suscripción del castigo Sao
that I've been with it for so many, many years
que ya llevo tantos tantos años con ello
and it's like they're trying to blackmail with
y es como que intentan chantajear con
that like Yes if you're going to talk about
eso en plan de Sí si vas a hablar de
this I'll unfollow you and it's like I'm not going
esto Te dejo de seguir y es como no voy
to leave things as they are Yeah and then in
a dejar las cosas como son Sí y luego en
reality they're going to see the videos that I
realidad sí van a ver los vídeos que
upload But that happens to me a lot eh That
suba Pero eso me pasa a mí mucho eh Eso
happens to me a lot on TV Well but in
me pasa a mí mucho en tele Bueno pero en
all that happens in all areas eh Not
tod eso pasa en todos los ámbitos eh No
only with the kids in the honors it
solamente en la chavalería en la señoría
has also happened to me eh If you speak badly of
también me ha pasado eh Si hablas mal de
this I'll leave but it's not that anymore but
este me voy pero ya no es eso sino en
live man it's something that really pisses me
directos tío que es una cosa que me toca
off you can't imagine how
la [__] no te puedes imaginar como
before a while ago look because I
antes hace un rato que mira porque
was pending on the status that I was
estaba pendiente del estato que estaba
recording but moderators I didn't hold back a
grabando pero moderadores no os corté un
hair as soon as you see  an example like the one I'm
pelo en cuando veáis un ejemplo como el
going to mention to you kick him out on the [ __ ]
que os voy a mencionar echarlo a la [__]
street directly okay but kick him out
calle directamente vale pero echarlo
banned eh I was earlier recording the
baneado eh estaba yo antes grabando el
Daniel Sancho extract man that is the
extracto de Daniel Sancho tío que es el
topic that is hitting hard and that is
tema que está pegando fuerte que y que
going to last it already has 10 days left okay And
va a durar ya le quedan 10 días vale Y
that we are making the best content
que estamos haciendo el mejor contenido
the best coverage on the subject it has
la mejor cobertura sobre el tema se me
occurred to me that trium has uploaded a video
ha terciado que trium ha subido un vídeo
now While I am here live and I feel like it
ahora Estando yo aquí en directo y me
and I am going to say it here
sale de la punta y lo voy a decir aquí
eh Because here I do not care to talk like this I feel like
eh Porque aquí me da igual hablar así me
recording an
sale de la punta de la [__] grabar un
exat for television gossip I feel like
exat para teles saldeo me sale de la
recording it But why can't
[__] grabarlo Pero por qué no voy a
I record an extract in my live broadcast
poder yo en mi directo grabar un extract
Even if it goes to the other channel
Aunque vaya para para el otro canal e
but what is it that it is an exzo that
pero que es que es un exzo que a lo
maybe I am going to upload it with gossip and
mejor lo voy a subir enre salseo y a lo
maybe it will get 100,000 visits I am going to
mejor va a [__] 100,000 visitas voy a
gain 100 Why can't I dedicate 15
ganar 100 Por qué no puedo dedicar 15
minutes to record this that soyas that
minutos a grabar este que soyas que en
live I will not have time to record a
directo no me va dar tiempo ya de grabar
clip for tesa for seo for tomorrow that
clip para tesa al seo para mañana que
all the  [ __ ] day we don't have any other
todo el [__] día no tenemos ningún otro
topic either the truth is today that is eh
tema tampoco la verdad hoy que sea eh la
if we were here that we had a
si estuviéramos aquí que tuviéramos un
topic that was the host the topics that are
tema que fuera la [__] los temas que
here today are being very banal
hay aquí hoy están siendo muy banales
I am spending time here on many
estoy echando aquí el rato en muchas
occasions no eh In order not to abandon
ocasiones no eh Para no dejar abandonar
the channel the truth is today's topics
el canal la verdad los temas de hoy
are weak the salcor youtuber has been going for
están flojitos el salcor youtuber lleva
a while that if it's not
una temporadita que como no sea el
Dallas who suddenly gets off his ass and decides to
Dallas que coja de repente y le dé por
mess with someone or me stirring up the
meterse con alguien o yo moviendo el
hornet's nest because I got this from this got this from that
avispero porque saque este de esto saque
the gossip doesn't move
esto de lo otro el salseo no se mueve
what are you telling me you don't talk about
que me estáis diciendo a mí no hablas de
this talk about that but you're
esto habla lo otro pero que os interesan
only interested in kids' topics like if
solamente temas de niños chicos de si
Spring tells the other I don't know what we
Spring le dice al otro no sé qué se
talk about everything that comes up no we
habla de todo lo que se tercia no que se
talk about everything well telling me about what I
habla de todo pues diciéndome a mí de lo
have that what I have no
que yo tengo que de lo que yo tengo no
this don't talk about that that's there I if
esto no lo hable eso eso allí yo si
now I want to stand here and record a
ahora me quiero poner aquí a grabar un
stranger from Belén Esteban I record it and
extrao de Belén Esteban lo grabo y están
the idiots are there but the people who
los imbéciles ahí pero la gente que no
aren't even members who surely are  people
son ni miembro que seguramente son gente
who come step I'm not going to leave I've
que viene paso no voy a dejar lo he
said it well I'm not going to stop talking about
dicho bien no voy a dejar de hablar de
things as they are I'm not going to stop
las cosas como son no voy a dejar de
expressing the things that seem fair
expresar las cosas que me parecen justas
and correct to me and I don't care about the people who are
y correctas y me da igual la gente que
dedicated to using the subscription of
se dedica a usar la suscripción del
punishment and all this nonsense because it's
castigo y tod estas tonterías porque es
like before above all I prefer to
como antes por encima de todo prefiero
stay with literally zero zero
quedarme con literalmente cero cero
followers than to do something with what
seguidores que hacer algo con lo que me
seems to me to be an [ __ ] and
parece que es una [__] y se viene
also another surprise video is coming from a
además otro vídeo sorpresa de un
character that every time I talk about
personaje de que cada vez que hablo de
him I get a lot of hate but I'm going to do it
él me cae mucho hate per lo voy a hacer
anyway I'm going to do it
de todas maneras voy hacer de todas
anyway because you're really going to freak out
maneras porque vais de verdad a flipar
about what I found out and it
de lo que me he enterado y pone al
reveals once again that I was
descubierto una vez más que yo tenía
right it's really always the
razón de verdad es que siempre es todo
same all the time Oh dasas he already apologized
el rato lo mismo Ay dasas ya se disculpó
Poor Herman German damn German You're
Pobrecito herman Germán [__] Germán Vais
really going to freak out I tell you You're really going to freak out freak out a lot a
a flipar de verdad os digo Vais a flipar
lot eh eh a lot
flipar de verdad mucho mucho eh eh mucho
You're going to affirm with the gods that are coming
Vais a afmar con los díos que se vienen
guys they're going to be very very very strong
chicos van a estar muy muy muy fuertes
but very very very strong Eh I'm not going to tell you
pero muy muy muy fuertes Eh no os digo
about who  it's coming but I'm telling you that they're
sobre quién viene pero os digo que se
going to get really burned and there's going to be
van a arder muchísimo y van a estar
a lot of these clowns trying to
muchos de estos payasos intentando
fully defend this dirty character
defender a full a este sucio personaje
but what I have is eh more than obvious
pero lo que tengo es eh más que evidente
and it's one more thing I told you again In Your
y es un más te lo dije otra vez In Your
Face again because it's literally
Face de nuevo porque literal es es
explicit, I mean it's mind-blowing that video is going to be
explícito o sea es flipante ese vídeo va
hard eh it's going to be hard and so it's
a dar fuerte eh va a dar fuerte y así
going to be like always I'm going to get a
que va serlo de siempre me va caer un
lot of sko people saying oh I was
montón de sko gente diciendo ay yo era
pambisito the classic one as always eh but these are
pambisito la clásica de siempre eh pero
things that I'm going to do I'm not going to stop
son cosas que voy a hacer no voy a dejar
doing them and and I'm really telling you
de hacerlas y y de verdad os lo digo en
seriously You're going to freak out You're going to freak out and it's going to
serio Vais a flipar Vais a flipar i va a
be one again I told you again
ser un de nuevo te lo dije otra vez más
they called me crazy again again the
me llamaron loco otra vez más otra vez
same thing and I'm telling you it's going to get a lot lot lot of
lo mismo y ya os digo va a caer mucho
hate but a lot of hate
mucho mucho mucho hate pero mucho hate
eh it's going to get but I'm going to do it
eh va a caer pero lo pienso hacer De
Anyway I'm telling you that it's coming
todas maneras ya os digo que se viene
strong and prepared for a few days or it's
fuerte y preparado por unos días o es
German or it's German it could be the Demented one it
Germán o es Germán puede ser el Demente
could be the Demented one that the Demented one has
puede ser el Demente que el Demente
been in the mouths of the people lately
últimamente está en Boca de la gente no
we haven't spoken I've had  here for several days
hemos hablado he tenido aquí varios días
a few videos because the Madman
un algunos vídeos porque el Demente
uploaded the Madman uploaded like a video the
subió el Demente subió como un vídeo el
Madman 2024 the end we didn't see it it lasts
Demente 2024 el fin no lo vimos sea dura
50 minutes but I don't know if it talks about something
50 minutos pero no sé si habla de algo
controversial no but this wasn't the one I was going to
polémico no pero no era este el que iba
see I've been here two or three times to post
a ver He esta dos o tres veces por poner
a video that they've made they've been
un vídeo que le han hecho que le han
making several videos about him
estado haciendo varios vídeos en la
last week and this two or
última en la última semana y esta dos o
three times but in the end we got
tres veces pero al final nos hemos
caught up in something else or just
enrollado con otra cosa o simplemente me
the issue I had with my throat and
el tema que tenía yo con la garganta y
the tone I think it was this I think it was
la tón creo que era este creo que fue
this one I was going to see but what am I
este el que iba a ver pero qué es lo que
telling you I mean the Madman Well look the
te digo o sea el Demente Pues mira el
Madman apologized to you and there are people who
Demente te disculpó y hay gente que a lo
maybe justify it in He apologized maybe
mejor lo justifica en Se disculpó a lo
not but I think it's because of Germán
mejor no pero yo creo que es por Germán
I think it's because Germán has everything has
yo creo que es por Germán tiene tod
all the tip predictions These
tiene toda la punta predicciones Esto sí
are predictions Wilson My poor
son predicciones Wilson Pobrecito mío
churra can I send you two memes that I made
churra puedo mandarte dos memes que hice
about you Send it come on tag me on
sobre ti Mándalo venga etiquétame en
Twitter and we'll see it right now run
Twitter y lo vemos ahora mismo ya corre
eh run ISO by with which he was leaving to
eh corre ISO by con que se iba para
promote his animated series  that it's going to
promocionar su serie animada a que va a
be an animated series in that video. He
ser una serie animada al D en ese vídeo
also criticized Willy re and that he
También criticó a Willy re y que se
found out things that he can't say. Yes,
enteró de cosas que no puede decir sí
but let's go, the one that fits me the most is
pero vamos a mí el que me cuadra más es
Germán. To me, I didn't like Germán, I didn't
el Germán a m a mí Germán no me gustó no
like him at all. eh, Germán, how he handled
me gustó un pelo eh Germán como gestionó
everything last year. eh, eh, the truth
todo lo del año pasado eh eh la verdad
is that he was very decisive. I thought he was a
es que fue muy decion me crea que era
good guy, to be honest. But he treated them in a
buen chico la verdad Pero los ó de
pathetic, cystic way. Oh
manera pateti quística Oh
[Music]
[Música]